https://freshspace.co.uk/privacy-policy/

HOMEWORKSERVICESABOUT USCONTACTPrivacy PolicyIf you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@freshspace.co.uk.At www.freshspace.co.uk, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.freshspace.co.uk and how it is used.LOG FILESLike many other Web sites, www.freshspace.co.uk makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of web browser, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.COOKIESwww.freshspace.co.uk does use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.INFORMATION COLLECTEDWe collect information from you when you submit the contact form on our site.When submitting the contact form on our web site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.DO WE USE COOKIES?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognise your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLYThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.YOUR CONSENTBy using our site, you consent to the above terms of our privacy policy.
